# Ramaldi Putra

ramaldiputra@gmail.com | | 310 946 2133 | Elmhurst, NY 11373

#### **Summary**

An undergraduate from Binus International University, Indonesia with a degree in Computer Science and concentration in game design and development with two years of experience in Back-end web development working with SQL, PHP Language and its frameworks, namely Codelgniter, Laravel. Currently looking for an opportunity to work in Fullstack-Development. A team-player with great communication skills and passion to learn.

### **Experiences**

Ben's Crab 08/2019 – Present

Oceanside, NY

Food Runner, Expeditor and Driver

- Responsible for organizing kitchen tickets to ensure the sequence of the order is accurate, garnishing the dishes, ensuring the dishes meet the quality standard, and transporting them from the kitchen to customers.
- Assist and communicate with customers needs, such as issues with the order to the server.
- Maintain calm and communicate with kitchen staff during peak hours.
- Responsible for cleaning the restaurant including the restrooms after closing.
- Work closely with the kitchen staff to ensure a fully-stocked kitchen, perform quality checks of the inventory, and communicate with the manager for low stock items.
- Responsible for checking the accuracy of the weekly delivery and report to the manager for any discrepancies.
- Responsible for employee pick-up, drop-off, and maintenance of the vehicle.

Tool Shop 06/2016 – 08/2016

Jakarta, Indonesia

Freelance Back-End Web Developer

- Developed sales dashboard web-application that automatically updates the inventory and total sales after each transaction.
- Responsible for project planning and delegating tasks to other team members.
- Conducted a daily meeting with team members to discuss the progress and obstacles for the project completion.
- Collaborated in preparation for the presentation of the final product.
- Utilized Laravel Framework and SQL.
- Completed the project within the agreed timeline of two months.

Puri Avia 11/2015 – 02/2016

Jakarta, Indonesia

Freelance Back-End Web Developer

- Developed Employee Task Report System for the company leadership to assign tasks and report the work.
- Utilized SQL Database Management System to develop the login credentials, report system and database, Codelgniter, and Bootstrap.

- Worked with two team members, collaborated with the team leader in preparation of the start of the project.
- Provided a monthly report of the project progress to the company owner.
- Presented the functionalities of the finished product and provided a demonstration.
- Applied feedback received to improve the interface prior to launch.
- Completed the project within the four months timeline.

Artoncode 10/2015 – 01/2016

Jakarta, Indonesia

Game Programmer Internship

- Assigned to an ongoing video game project to develop gameplay.
- Responsible for completing at least one gameplay per day as assigned by the project lead.
- Provided a daily report on the progress of the task to the project lead and made changes according to the feedback.
- Utilized Trello, to track the ongoing or completed progress of a game feature monitored by the project lead.
- Utilized Github for tracking coding progress on the project.
- Length of internship: four months.

TUV Rheinland 08/2015 - 11/2015

Jakarta, Indonesia

Freelance Back-End Web Developer

- Developed Company Rating System for PPP-Einstein and Rating System Functionalities.
- Utilized CodeIgniter and Radar Charts.
- Responsible for developing the charts and its variables (including sub-variables) using Bootstrap.
- Collaborate with other team members and leader for task assignments based on each person's skillset.
- Attended weekly meetings with the project manager and reported the progress of the project based on the assigned tasks.
- Completed the project within the timeline of three months.

### <u>Skills</u>

- HTML
- CSS
- PHP
- Laravel Framework
- CodeIgniter Framework
- SQL
- Unity Game Engine

## **Educations**

B.S. in Computer Science – June 2016

Concentration: Game Design and Development

Binus International University, Jakarta